Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - G
        - Giant Steps - Into you, 1988; SR-14564; Giant Steps (Box 278)
          Catalog # SP-12286; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012286 A ES-1
          A&M Records
        - Giant Wheel - Retrash; How deep is the ocean?, 1995; SR-14565; Giant Wheel (Box 278)
          Catalog # SR12378; A-side Matrix # SR-12378-A
          Strictly Rhythm
        - Giants - Giants, 1978; SR-14566; Giants (Box 278)
          Catalog # MCA-3188; A-side Matrix # MCA-1988 CR-1
          LAX Records
          Canada
        - Giants Of The City - Get busy, 1987; SR-14567; Giants Of The City (Box 278)
          Catalog # BB1987; A-side Matrix # BB-1987-A
          Giants Of The City Music
        - Gibb, Robin - Boys do fall in love, 1984; SR-14568; Gibb, Robin (Box 278)
          Catalog # DMD 740; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46329-1
          Mirage
        - Gibb, Robin - Secret agent; Robot, 1984; SR-14569; Gibb, Robin (Box 278)
          Catalog # DMD 775; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46691-1
        - Gibson - Cuba, 1978; SR-14570; Gibson (Box 278)
          Catalog # PRO-A809; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1-809-A2 B-14091
          Island Records
        - Gibson, Debbie - Only in my dreams, 1987; SR-14571; Gibson, Debbie (Box 278)
          Catalog # A9322TP; A-side Matrix # A-9322-TP-A
        - Gift Of Dreams - Funkincise, 1982; SR-14572; Gift Of Dreams (Box 278)
          Catalog # JP-12-004DJ; A-side Matrix # JP-12-004-ADJ
          Jam Power Records
          Northridge, California
        - Gifted - Rock me tonight, 1988; SR-14573; Gifted (Box 278)
          Catalog # PAP 12003; A-side Matrix # PAP 12003 A
          Tri Boro
        - Gifted One - Brooklyn Kids, 1995; SR-14574; Gifted One (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14574. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PRO 1162-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1162-1-A
        - Gifted One - Brooklyn Kids, 1995; SR-14575; Gifted One (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14573. Multiple copies.
        - Giggalow Gee - Doctor feel good, SR-14576; Giggalow Gee (Box 278)
          Catalog # GG-1; A-side Matrix # GG-1-A
          Giggie Entertainment
        - Giggles - I will survive, SR-14577; Giggles (Box 278)
          Catalog # MRC 04522; A-side Matrix # MRC-4522-A
          Metropolitan Recording Corporation
        - Gill, Johnny - Tell me how u want it, 1994; SR-14578; Gill, Johnny (Box 278)
          Catalog # 374631162-1; A-side Matrix # 374631162-1A+RC1
        - Gill, Johnny - It's your body, 1996; SR-14579; Gill, Johnny; Troutman, Roger (Box 278)
          Catalog # 374632017-1; A-side Matrix # 374632017-1-A SP1
        - Gill, Johnny - Love in an elevator, 1997; SR-14580; Gill, Johnny (Box 279)
          Catalog # 374632028-1; A-side Matrix # 374632028-1-A1
        - Gill, Johnny - The floor (remix), 1993; SR-14581; Gill, Johnny (Box 279)
          Catalog # 374631095-1; A-side Matrix # 374631095-1-A
        - Gill, Johnny - Rub you the right way, 1990; SR-14582; Gill, Johnny (Box 279)
          Catalog # L33-17921; A-side Matrix # MOT-9142 FDS-2
        - Gina Go-Go - I can't face the fact, 1988; SR-14583; Gina Go-Go (Box 279)
          Catalog # V-15396; A-side Matrix # V-1-15396-21
        - Gina Go-Go - I can't face the fact, 1988; SR-14584; Gina Go-Go (Box 279)
        - Gino - ¡Te quiero ya!, 1997; SR-14585; Gino; Thoka (Box 279)
          Catalog # DOS 057; A-side Matrix # DOS 057 A1
          Dos Or Die Recordings
        - Ginuwine - Hell yeah, 2003; SR-14586; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          Catalog # EAS 59148; A-side Matrix # XSS-591484A-1B
        - Ginuwine - Hell yeah, 2003; SR-14587; Ginuwine (Box 279)
        - Ginuwine - Pony, 1996; SR-14588; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          Catalog # XPR 3101; A-side Matrix # 31 3101 20 1A1
        - Ginuwine - 100% Ginuwine (Disc one), 1999; SR-14589; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-14590. Double album.
          Catalog # B2 69598; A-side Matrix # AL-69905-1A
          550 Music
        - Ginuwine - 100% Ginuwine (Disc two), 1999; SR-14590; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-14589. Double album.
          Catalog # B2 69598; A-side Matrix # AL-69906-1A
        - Ginuwine - 100% Ginuwine (Disc one), 1999; SR-14591; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-14592. Double album.
        - Ginuwine - 100% Ginuwine (Disc two), 1999; SR-14592; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-14591. Double album.
        - Ginuwine - Tribute to a woman, 2001; SR-14593; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          Catalog # EAS 56762; A-side Matrix # XSS 56762
        - Ginuwine - When doves cry, 1996; SR-14594; Ginuwine (Box 279)
          Catalog # BAS 0921; A-side Matrix # XSS921A-1B
        - Giorgio & Chris - Love's in you, love's in me, 1978; SR-14595; Giorgio & Chris; Moroder, Giorgio; Bennett, Chris (Box 279)
          Catalog # NBLP 7104 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7104-AS
          Casablanca
        - Gipsy Kings - Ami wa wa (masters at work mixes), 1997; SR-14596; Gipsy Kings (Box 279)
          Catalog # 0-79480; A-side Matrix # ST-DM 87233-87234-1
        - Gipsy Kings - Gipsy Kings, 1988; SR-14597; Gipsy Kings (Box 279)
          Catalog # 60845-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60845-A-DMM-1
          Elektra
        - Gipsy Kings - Mosaique, 1989; SR-14598; Gipsy Kings (Box 279)
          Catalog # 60892-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60892-ADMM-1
          Mosaique
          Brazil
        - Gipsy Kings - Bamboleo, 1988; SR-14599; Gipsy Kings (Box 279)
          Catalog # 0-66175; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66715A-3
        - Gipsy Kings - Gipsy Kings, 1989; SR-16158; Gipsy Kings (Box 279)
          Catalog # STAR 2355; A-side Matrix # 1150191 A 12C2
          Telstar
        - Girl! - Fired up, 1993; SR-16159; Girl! (Box 279)
          Catalog # EB 016; A-side Matrix # EB-016 AA
          Eightball Records
        - Girl Eats Boy - Girl Eats Boy, 1997; SR-16160; Girl Eats Boy (Box 279)
          Catalog # DUKE 034; A-side Matrix # DUKE 024-A1
          Hydrogen Dukebox
        - Girl Talk - Dance with me baila baila, 1988; SR-16161; Girl Talk (Box 279)
          Catalog # GS 5000; A-side Matrix # GS-5000-A
          Skyyline Records
        - Girlfriend - Lay your love on the line, SR-16162; Girlfriend (Box 279)
          Catalog # AIM 12104; A-side Matrix # AIM 12104 A RE1
          AIM Records
          Fairfield, Connecticut
        - Girlfriends - Jammin new wave (going to a fabulous party), 1984; SR-16163; Girlfriends; Reynolds, Margaret (Box 279)
          Catalog # GLFD-1003; A-side Matrix # GLFD-1003 BMJ-1616
          BMJ Records
        - Girls - S-E-S-E-X, 1984; SR-16164; Girls (Box 279)
          Catalog # 44 05091; A-side Matrix # XSS-173015-B
        - Girls can't help it - Baby doll, 1983; SR-16165; Girls can't help it (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16166. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 0-29773; A-side Matrix # 0-29773-A-SH1
        - Girls can't help it - Baby doll, 1983; SR-16166; Girls can't help it (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16165. Multiple copies.
        - Girls on the block - Little bicho, 1988; SR-16167; Girls on the block (Box 279)
          Catalog # CR12-031; A-side Matrix # CR-12-031-A
          Criminal Records
        - Giscombe, Norman, Jr. - Get up and dance, 1981; SR-16168; Giscombe, Norman, Jr. (Box 279)
          Catalog # FST-1452; A-side Matrix # FST-1452-A
          Fire-Sign Limited
        - Gitta - No more turning back, SR-16169; Gitta (Box 279)
          Catalog # 92507.OP; A-side Matrix # 925 0570 A1
          Jive
        - Glamco Productions - Jazzy grooves vol. 1, 1991; SR-13792; Glamco Productions (Box 279)
          Catalog # EB 003; A-side Matrix # EB003-A
        - Glass - Let me feel you heartbeat, 1982; SR-16170; Glass (Box 279)
          Catalog # WES-22145; A-side Matrix # WES-22145A 70515-1A
        - Glass - Bedrok, 1983; SR-16171; Glass; Williams, John (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16172. Different discs.
          Catalog # HCS-10150; A-side Matrix # HCS-10150-1A
          Houston Connection Recording Corporation
        - Glass - Bedrok, 1983; SR-16172; Glass; Williams, John (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16171. Different discs.
          Catalog # HLP-20014; A-side Matrix # HLP-22014-A
        - Glass, Philip - Glassworks, 1982; SR-16173; Glass, Philip (Box 279)
          Catalog # FM 37265; A-side Matrix # MAL-37265-1B
        - Glasswurk - She works her body right, 1990; SR-16174; Glasswurk (Box 279)
          Catalog # MCA-23949; A-side Matrix # MCA 8875 FDS-2
        - Glitter, Gary - Ready to rock, 1991; SR-16175; Glitter, Gary (Box 279)
          Catalog # OY1T; A-side Matrix # OY 1TA-1
          Attitude
        - Glitter, Gary - Always yours, 1985; SR-16176; Glitter, Gary (Box 279)
          Catalog # DOJOLP 20; A-side Matrix # B-3701A-1
          Dojo
        - Glitter, Gary - Red hot (reputation), 1990; SR-16177; Glitter, Gary; Gang (Box 279)
          Catalog # VST 1320; A-side Matrix # VST 1320 A-1U-1-2
          Virgin
        - Glitter, Gary - Rock and rool (parts 1 & 2); Na na hey hey kiss him goodbye, 1991; SR-16178; Glitter, Gary; Steam (Box 279)
          Catalog # SPEC-1620; A-side Matrix # SPEC-1620-A
          Unidisc
        - Glitter, Gary - The leader, 1974; SR-16179; Glitter, Gary (Box 279)
          Catalog # EPC 32200; A-side Matrix # EPC-32200-A4
        - Glitter Band - Makes you blind, 1975; SR-16180; Glitter Band (Box 279)
          Catalog # AL 4109; A-side Matrix # AL 4109-SA-RE2
        - Glitter, Gary - Glitter and gold, 1980; SR-16181; Glitter, Gary (Box 279)
          Catalog # 3E 36848; A-side Matrix # TAL 36848
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Get ridiculous, 1986; SR-16182; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E. (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16183. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BR-0004; A-side Matrix # BR-0004-A
          Body Rock
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Get ridiculous, 1986; SR-16183; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E. (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16182. Multiple copies.
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Celebrate! (Everybody), 1985; SR-16184; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Globe; Pow Wow (Box 279)
          Catalog # TB 857; A-side Matrix # TB-857-A
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Celebrate! (Everybody), 1985; SR-16185; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Globe; Pow Wow (Box 279)
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Play that beat Mr. D.J., 1983; SR-16186; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; G.L.O.B.E. & Whiz Kid (Box 279)
          Catalog # TB 836; A-side Matrix # TB 836 A
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Play that beat Mr. D.J., 1983; SR-16187; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; G.L.O.B.E. & Whiz Kid (Box 279)
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Play that beat Mr. D.J., 1983; SR-16188; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; G.L.O.B.E. & Whiz Kid (Box 279)
        - G.L.O.B.E. - Play that beat Mr. D.J., 1983; SR-16189; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E.; G.L.O.B.E. & Whiz Kid (Box 279)
        - Glory - Let's get nice, 1981; SR-16190; Glory (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16191. Different discs.
          Catalog # POS-1204; A-side Matrix # POS-1204-A-1660
          Posse Records
        - Glory - Let's get nice, 1981; SR-16191; Glory (Box 279)
          In same jacket as # SR-16190. Different discs.
        - Glory - Let's get nice, 1981; SR-16192; Glory (Box 279)
        - Glory - Let's get nice, 1981; SR-16193; Glory (Box 279)
        - Glory - Let's get nice, 1981; SR-16194; Glory (Box 280)
        - Glover, Roger - Fake it, 1984; SR-16195; Glover, Roger (Box 280)
          Catalog # PRO 308-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 308-1
          21 Records
        - Gnarls Barkley - Smiley faces, 2006; SR-16196; Gnarls Barkley (Box 280)
          Catalog # 0-104444; A-side Matrix # ST-AT-104444-A1
          Downtown
        - Gnarls Barkley - Crazy, 2006; SR-16197; Gnarls Barkley (Box 280)
          Catalog # PR 302155; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302155A-1
          Downtown Music
        - Gnarls Barkley - Crazy, 2006; SR-16198; Gnarls Barkley (Box 280)
        - Gnawa Music Of Marrakesh - Night spirit masters, 1990; SR-16199; Gnawa Music Of Marrakesh (Box 280)
          Catalog # 539 881-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-881-1-AS-SP
          Axiom
        - Go-Go's - We got the beat, 1981; SR-16200; Go-Go's (Box 280)
          Catalog # SP-70959; A-side Matrix # AMSP070959-A T1
          I.R.S. Records
        - Go-Go Allstarz - Do the whop, 1984; SR-16201; Go-Go Allstarz (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16202. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # DT 1004; A-side Matrix # DT-1004-A
          D.E.T.T. Records
          Landover, Maryland
        - Go-Go Allstarz - Do the whop, 1984; SR-16202; Go-Go Allstarz (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16201. Multiple copies.
        - Go Go Posse - D.C. don't stand for dodge city, 1988; SR-16203; Go Go Posse (Box 280)
          Catalog # IHY-1001; A-side Matrix # IHY-1001-A
          I Hear Ya! Records
          Washington, D.C.
        - Go Go Posse - D.C. don't stand for dodge city, 1988; SR-16204; Go Go Posse (Box 280)
        - Go West - Eye to eye, 1985; SR-16205; Go West (Box 280)
          Catalog # 4V9 42900; A-side Matrix # 4V9 42900 ACP 1
        - Goats - Typical american; Burn the flag, 1992; SR-16206; Goats (Box 280)
          Catalog # 44 74726; A-side Matrix # XSS-74726-A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records
        - Goats - Rumblefish, 1994; SR-16207; Goats (Box 280)
          Catalog # CAS 6714; A-side Matrix # XSS 6714A
        - God Within - Crucial introspection part two, 1999; SR-16208; God Within; Hardkiss, Scott (Box 280)
          Catalog # 54295-0; A-side Matrix # 54295A
          Sunburn Records
          San Diego, California
        - Godfather Of Wierd - Theme from wierd; Lazy days, 1996; SR-16209; Godfather Of Wierd (Box 280)
          Catalog # ruf 011; A-side Matrix # RUF 011 A
          The Ruf Label
          Altrincham, United Kingdom
        - Godley & Creme - Cry, 1985; SR-16210; Godley & Creme (Box 280)
          Catalog # 881 786-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 881-786-1-85-NP-L939-ALD
        - Godley & Creme - Snack attack; The party, 1981; SR-16211; Godley & Creme (Box 280)
          Catalog # DMD 322; A-side Matrix # STDM-40882-1
        - Godmoma - Taste of magic, 1981; SR-16212; Godmoma (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16213. Multiple copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # AS-11525; A-side Matrix # AM-11525-A-1-SP
        - Godmoma - Taste of magic, 1981; SR-16213; Godmoma (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16212. Multiple copies. Annotated.
        - God's Property - You are the only one, 1997; SR-16214; God's Property; Kirk Franklin's Nu Nation (Box 280)
          Catalog # INT8P 6245; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6245-A
          B-Rite Music
          Inglewood, California
        - God's Property - You are the only one, 1997; SR-16215; God's Property; Kirk Franklin's Nu Nation (Box 280)
        - Godwin, Peter - Images of heaven, 1982; SR-16216; Godwin, Peter (Box 280)
          Catalog # PX-1-504; A-side Matrix # PX 1504 Aside
        - Godwin, Peter - Images of heaven, 1982; SR-16217; Godwin, Peter (Box 280)
        - Godwin, Peter - Baby's in the mountains, 1983; SR-16218; Godwin, Peter (Box 280)
          Catalog # PRO 228-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 228-1-83-NP-6494-PRC-C-1-1
        - Godwin, Peter - Baby's in the mountains, 1983; SR-16219; Godwin, Peter (Box 280)
        - Goff, Ivan - 90's goin' hard, 1992; SR-16220; Goff, Ivan; Brown, Chuck (Box 280)
          Catalog # IG 777; A-side Matrix # IG 777 A
          Goff Records
        - Gold, Lori - I likes it (remix), 1995; SR-16221; Gold, Lori (Box 280)
          Catalog # CR-337-DJ; A-side Matrix # CR-337-A
          Cutting Records
        - Gold, Lori - I likes it (remix), 1995; SR-16222; Gold, Lori (Box 280)
        - Gold Money - A day in the life of a player, 1992; SR-16223; Gold Money (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16224. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # TB 1043; A-side Matrix # 1-1043A
        - Gold Money - A day in the life of a player, 1992; SR-16224; Gold Money (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16223. Multiple copies.
        - Gold Orchestra - Sousa's salsa (that tuba thing), 1976; SR-16225; Gold Orchestra (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16226. Different discs.
          Catalog # 1220B; A-side Matrix # 1220-A
          Gold Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Gold Orchestra - Sousa's salsa (that tuba thing), 1976; SR-16226; Gold Orchestra (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16225. Different discs.
          Catalog # 1220A; A-side Matrix # 1220-A
        - Gold Teet - Searching for love, 1995; SR-16227; Gold Teet (Box 280)
          Catalog # 72392 78012 1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78012-1-A
        - Gold Teet - The heat is on, 1995; SR-16228; Gold Teet (Box 280)
          Catalog # SBAB-75455-1; A-side Matrix # SBAB-75455-1-A
        - Gold Teet - Searching for love, 1995; SR-16229; Gold Teet (Box 280)
        - Gold, Xaviera - Bad girls, 1995; SR-16230; Gold, Xaviera (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16231. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BB003; A-side Matrix # BB-003-A
          Basement Boys Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Gold, Xaviera - Bad girls, 1995; SR-16231; Gold, Xaviera (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16230. Multiple copies.
        - Golden Eagles - Lightning and thunder, 1988; SR-16232; Golden Eagles (Box 280)
          Catalog # Rounder Records 2073; A-side Matrix # ROU 2073-A
          Rounder Records
          Burlington, Massachusetts
        - Golden Eagles - Lightning and thunder, 1988; SR-16233; Golden Eagles (Box 280)
        - Golden Earring - Twilight zone, 1982; SR-16234; Golden Earring (Box 280)
          Catalog # 2.105; A-side Matrix # 2105 A 30C2
        - Golden Girls - Too cute, 1985; SR-16235; Golden Girls (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16236. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # TB 860; A-side Matrix # TB-860-A
        - Golden Girls - Too cute, 1985; SR-16236; Golden Girls (Box 280)
          In same jacket as # SR-16235. Multiple copies.
        - Golden Girls - Too cute, 1985; SR-16237; Golden Girls (Box 280)
        - Golden Girls - Too cute, 1985; SR-16238; Golden Girls (Box 280)
        - Golden Girls - Too cute, 1985; SR-16239; Golden Girls (Box 280)
        - Goldie - Digital (Disc one), 1997; SR-16240; Goldie; KRS One (Box 280)
          Catalog # FXDJX 316; A-side Matrix # FXDJX 316 A
          FFRR
        - Goldy - Nuthin' but a tramp, 1994; SR-16241; Goldy (Box 280)
          Catalog # JDAB-42271-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42271-1-A1
        - Goldy - Nuthin' but a tramp, 1994; SR-16242; Goldy (Box 280)
        - Gonzalez, Al - A taster 12'' from the forthcoming compilation jazz latino, 2002; SR-16243; Gonzalez, Al; Guito Y Su ConJunto; Morales, Teodoro (Box 280)
          Catalog # RJ003; A-side Matrix # RJ-003-A
          Re-Joint Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Gonzalez, Pee - Sozy-kaizer, 1997; SR-16244; Gonzalez, Pee (Box 280)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # S'024 KAISRT''-A
          9mm Recordz
          Belgium
        - Gonzalez, Terri - How good it is; Caught up (in one night love affairs), 1980; SR-15245; Gonzalez, Terri (Box 280)
          Catalog # EAR-102; A-side Matrix # EAR-102A
          Eastbourne Records Ltd.
        - Gonzalez, Terri - How good it is, 1980; SR-16246; Gonzalez, Terri (Box 281)
          Catalog # Eastbourne 101; A-side Matrix # EAR-101-AM
        - Gonzalez, Terri - Treat yourself to my love, 1981; SR-16247; Gonzalez, Terri (Box 281)
          Catalog # BKD-507; A-side Matrix # BKD-507-A
          Becket Records
        - Gonzalez, Terri - Is there rockin' in this house, 1987; SR-16248; Gonzalez, Terri (Box 281)
          Catalog # DMD 1083; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-52422-52421-3
        - Gonzalez, Terri - Born a winner, 1982; SR-16249; Gonzalez, Terri (Box 281)
          Catalog # BKD-510; A-side Matrix # BKD-510-A
        - Good Girls - Your sweetness, 1989; SR-16250; Good Girls (Box 281)
          Catalog # L33-17911; A-side Matrix # MOT 9088 FDS 1
        - Good Girls - It must be love, 1992; SR-16251; Good Girls (Box 281)
          Catalog # 3746310831; A-side Matrix # 37463-1083-1A
        - Goodfellaz - Sugar honey ice tea, 1996; SR-16252; Goodfellaz (Box 281)
          Catalog # PRPRO 00329; A-side Matrix # PRPRO 00329 A1-SP1
          Avatar
        - Goodie - You and I, 1982; SR-16253; Goodie (Box 281)
          Catalog # TK 227; A-side Matrix # TK-227-2-56923
        - Goodie - Do something, 1982; SR-16254; Goodie (Box 281)
          Catalog # MK 205; A-side Matrix # MK 205-25922-LONG-PRC-C1-1
        - Goodie Mob - World party (Disc one), 1999; SR-16255; Goodie Mob (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16256. Double album.
          Catalog # 73008-26064-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-26064-1-SARE AA-BAU
          LaFace Records
        - Goodie Mob - World party (Disc two), 1999; SR-16256; Goodie Mob (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16255. Double album.
          Catalog # 73008-26064-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-26064-SC AA-BAU
        - Goodie Mob - They don't dance no mo', 1998; SR-16257; Goodie Mob (Box 281)
          Catalog # LFDP-4306; A-side Matrix # 73008-24306-1-SA
        - Goodie Mob - The world I know (country livin'); Sellin' D.O.P.E., 1998; SR-16258; Goodie Mob; Esthero; Dead Prez (Musical group) (Box 281)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # SLAM-A-DISC4
          Immortal Records
        - Goodie Mob - They don't dance no mo', 1998; SR-16259; Goodie Mob (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16260. Different discs.
        - Goodie Mob - They don't dance no mo', 1998; SR-16260; Goodie Mob (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16259. Different discs.
          Catalog # LFDP-4303-SB; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4303-SB
        - Goodie Mob - Cell therapy; Soul food; Benz or beamer, 1995; SR-16261; Goodie Mob; Outkast (Box 281)
          Catalog # 73008-24114-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24114-1-SA-RE 2
        - Goodman, Benny - The golden age of Benny Goodman, 1956; SR-16262; Goodman, Benny; Benny Goodman And His Orchestra (Box 281)
          Catalog # LPM-1099; A-side Matrix # F2 PP5346-6S
          RCA Victor
        - Goody Goody - Goody Goody, 1978; SR-16263; Goody Goody (Box 281)
          Catalog # SD 19197; A-side Matrix # ST-A-784123-D
        - Goody Goody - It looks like love; Super jock, 1978; SR-16264; Goody Goody (Box 281)
          Catalog # DSKO-150; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO33540-2
        - Goofy - Any thing can happen; Blizi blaw, 1997; SR-16265; Goofy; Red Rat (Box 281)
          Catalog # VPRD 6253; A-side Matrix # VPRD-6253-A
          Shines Records
        - Googie - Missing love, 1980; SR-16266; Googie; Coppola, Tom (Box 281)
          Catalog # 43 11294; A-side Matrix # XSS167293-1A
        - Goon Squad - Powerdrill, 1986; SR-16267; Goon Squad (Box 281)
          Catalog # 49-05297; A-side Matrix # XSS 174729 1A
        - Gooster - Zig zag zen (Disc one), 1996; SR-16268; Gooster (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16269. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 28DLP; A-side Matrix # UR 28/A
          Five Star Recordings
          Switzerland
        - Gooster - Zig zag zen (Disc two), 1996; SR-16269; Gooster (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16268. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 28DLP; A-side Matrix # UR 28/C
        - Gopher, Alex - Party people vol. 2, 1999; SR-16270; Gopher, Alex (Box 281)
          Catalog # SLD 020 EP2; A-side Matrix # SLD20EP2 A
          Disques Solid
        - Gopher, Alex - Time, 1999; SR-16271; Gopher, Alex (Box 281)
          Catalog # SLD 021 EP; A-side Matrix # SLD 21 EP A ZEDD
        - Gopher, Alex - Time, 1999; SR-16272; Gopher, Alex (Box 281)